<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ACBW Rolling around Tokyo</title>
    <link>https://acbw.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ACBW Rolling around Tokyo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://acbw.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Harumi Wharf</title>
      <link>https://acbw.me/blog/harumi-wharf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acbw.me/blog/harumi-wharf/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s February, although it was technically still winter, a very clear afternoon sky can be warm enough for you to go with just a T-shirt and a jacket. Being mindful not to stay outside until sundown, the zombies will *ehem the air will be too cold for only a thin jacket. I hadn&amp;rsquo;t ridden my bicycle often during winter. Clear sky weekends gave me hope that spring is just around the corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wadabori Park</title>
      <link>https://acbw.me/blog/wadabori-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acbw.me/blog/wadabori-park/</guid>
      <description>It is Autumn, getting colder for cycling around so I appreciate clear sunny weekends. Leaves are turning yellow, it is beautiful to see if you don’t have to worry about cleaning the fallen leaves. Since the Sunday was clear and sunny, time to get my red ride and yet again get lost in the beauty of the season.
This time, I wanted to go all the way to the shiba inu tobacco store clerk although knowing it has been retired from the job and living a life as a normal shiba dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Gate Bridge</title>
      <link>https://acbw.me/blog/tokyo-gate-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acbw.me/blog/tokyo-gate-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Today’s bicycle diary is catching the sunrise around the Tokyo Bay Area. I decided to ride all the way to Tokyo Gate Bridge.
Sunrise and sunset are the moment most people say ‘The Golden Hour’. You can get the natural lighting coming from the side which is best for dramatic shots, even cheap cameras can take breathtaking pictures and make your friends say ‘wow’.
Taking pictures while moving on a bicycle can be a challenge, most of them turn out to be blurry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tokyo Bay Aqua Line Entrance</title>
      <link>https://acbw.me/blog/tokyo-bay-aqua-line-entrance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acbw.me/blog/tokyo-bay-aqua-line-entrance/</guid>
      <description>This trip was a big motivation test on myself. I never rode long distances, and this time I got myself a fixed gear bike. My legs were only trained a couple of weeks. The weather was not pleasing. The Aqua Bay Line Entrance is for cars only, there was no guarantee I could cycle around the entrance either. They might fence out the whole area and would left me disappointed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossing the Rainbow Bridge</title>
      <link>https://acbw.me/blog/crossing-the-rainbow-bridge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acbw.me/blog/crossing-the-rainbow-bridge/</guid>
      <description>Odaiba, My first cycling adventure in Tokyo after I got my ride. Up until now I only have been there by riding trains. I cannot tell how far a place is going by that long metal snake on rails. It felt far.
I took a little detour along the way passing Tokyo Tower, love the nice clear sunny weather. Still not used by the traffic rules around, took longer than I should.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
